

Profile

I'm a skilled Full Stack Developer with a wealth of diverse life and technical experience that I bring to every project. I follow form as well as function. I know that the aesthetics of effective design combined with application speed, security and reliability combine to create a great user experience. I work quickly and effectively in getting things built and working across the stack. I'm an excellent communicator who thrives in bright and enthusiastic teams and I'm also a self starter when working solo.

Employment History

Freelance Software Developer at Self Employed, Torquay Devon UK February 2020 — Present

After 20 Years in the Catering Industry and due to a life long passion in all that regards I.T. I decided to take my self taught knowledge of programming languages to a professional level and have a career change. I now have confidence to embark on a various arrays of projects due to my proficiency in different languages and frameworks. My skills include Python, Java, JS, HTML5, CSS, CSS3, Flask, Django, MySql, MongoDB, Sqlite3, Heroku, Git...and much more.

Senior Sous Chef at Amici's Restaurant, Torquay

April 2017 — February 2020

- Oversaw all kitchen and food operations.
- Worked effectively with all workers, to promote a happy working environment.
- Managed allergies with care and professionalism for customer safety and satisfaction.
- Sourced elite food products, creating a better dining experience.

Head Chef at Margaret Clitherow Housing Ass., Torquay

April 2013 — April 2017

- Day to day running of the kitchen
- menu planing
- · staff training
- stock ordering
- · management.

Sous Chef at QB Mercato e Cucina, Milan Italy

June 2010 — April 2013

Assisting in the day to day running of the kitchen

- · menu planing
- staff training
- stock ordering
- management

Details

17 Shelley Avenue, Torquay, TQ1 4PG, United Kingdom, +44(0)7496656778 luigi76langella@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 07/03/1976 Naples

Nationality Italian

Driving license Yes

Links

Portfolio Linkedin Resume

Skills

Python

JavaScript

Django

HTML5

CSS

SASS MySql

MongoDB

Linux

CSS3

Python Flask

User Experience (UX)

Data Visualization

Java

Education

Full Stack Software Developer, Code Institute, On-line

October 2018 — February 2020

Code Institute's Diploma in Software Development is an intense coding bootcamp created and validated by tech industry experts and academics.

Pythonista, The Learning People, On-line

February 2020 — Present

Perfect stepping stone to becoming a Python developer or data scientist.

NVQ2 Cookery, South Devon College, Torquay

September 2010 — July 2011

Courses

Pythonista, The Learning People

February 2020 — Present

Full Stack Software Developer, Code Institute

October 2018 — February 2020

Complete Python Bootcamp, Udemy

January 2017 — September 2018

Python Beyond the Basics OOP

July 2018 — October 2018

Learn Python Programming MasterClass, Udemy

January 2016 — January 2017

◄ References

References available upon request

Y Extra-curricular activities

Java Tutorial for complete Beginners at Udemy

January 2017 — June 2017

Languages

Italian

English

Hobbies

Playing Guitar, Listening to music, Playing tennis.